Contact

jnaude60512@gmail.com LinkedIn GitHub

Top Skills

Time Series Forecasting Machine Learning Python

Certifications

- Time Series Analysis, Forecasting, and Machine Learning
- Python for Data Science and Machine Learning Bootcamp
- Higher Certificate in Information Systems (Software Development)
- Calculus I
- Data Science and Machine Learning Bootcamp with R

Public Contributions

- viss
- <u>SimpactCyan</u>
- <u>spatialedge-analytics-dfauditor</u>
- holidays
- LG-WebOS-Remote-Control
- MacbookPro14-2Ubuntu

Jean Naude

Machine Learning Engineer at Spatialedge (Pty) Ltd

Stellenbosch, Western Cape, South Africa

Summary

Senior Technical Lead as a Machine Learning Engineer with 5 years of experience in developing, deploying and optimizing machine learning models and taking them to production for large retail chains based in South Africa. Co-Founder of a non-profit that played a key role in developing open-source software for an international epidemiology simulation project that provided valuable insights to the World Health Organization.

My strength lies in getting to production quickly with observable, impactful results that facilitate business decision-making.

Experience

Spatialedge (Pty) Ltd

Machine Learning Engineer

Stellenbosch, Western Cape, South Africa June 2021 - Present (4+ years)

Exile AI (Pty) Ltd

Full-Stack Engineer

Cape Town, Western Cape, South Africa January 2024 - Present (1+ years)

Education

ESIEE PARIS

International Masters in Computer Science (Intelligent Systems), Machine Learning

2019 - 2021

Pearson Institute

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

2015 - 2018

Tech Stack

- Python
- Pytorch
- Scikit Learn
- C++
- CUDA
- C
- SQL
- Big Query

- Bash
- Git
- Docker
- CI/CD
- GCP
- Airflow
- Dagster
- Kubernetes
- Terraform
- Helm
- React
- TypeScript
- Redis DB
- Tensorflow
- Gitlab
- Linux

Interests

- Epidemiology
- Computer Vision
- Puzzle Games

• Musical Theory